Mom, have you seen Peter?
I am here at the warehouse
to warn Jin Ho.
Peter, come on!
Where is this going?
What are you doing here?
We just need to leave.
Now!
I need you to get out of here.
Why is there no one here?
You have nowhere left to run!
This is an ambush!
You look pretty happy.
I just had a big win today.
You knew they were coming!
Because you led them here!
My father. I need to get to him!
You are really going to charge
into the middle of a shootout?
I am not leaving
while my father is in there
fighting for his life!
Stop!
None of you are getting out
of here alive!
I do not want to die yet.
We need backup now!
[OBB]
[GUN FIRING IN DISTANCE]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Stop!
Kill them!
[GUN FIRING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Joey...
[GUN FIRING IN DISTANCE]
Jin Ho...
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing here?
Jin Ho, I cannot blame you
if you are angry with us.
But I heard you let
Peter escape.
So, that means you are
still on our side, right?
Jin Ho, please help me.
I need to get my father out.
I need to make sure he is alive.
I saw him.
He is alive.
Jin Ho, please help me.
We need to get my father out.
Please!
Help me.
Why should I?
You're lucky I haven't shot you.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You used me to get Liza!
Jin Ho, I know what they did
to my family.
I just want all of this to end.
And you want the same thing too,
don't you?
You used us to get to Liza!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUN FIRING IN DISTANCE]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Stop! Surrender now!
[GUN FIRES]
But I never put you in danger.
I helped you and protected you
while we were looking
for Liza together.
Maybe you were a true friend,
as much as you could be.
But I hope
you understand this too.
I have a family to protect,
Jin Ho!
At my expense?
I am sorry, Jin Ho.
I really am.
[GUN FIRING IN DISTANCE]
- Hey!
- Hey! Stop!
Hands up!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Come on, hands up!
Hands up!
Arrest them!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jin Ho!
At long last...
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
We finally meet, woman.
You are only brave
because you have a gun.
Try fighting without it.
Go ahead.
Let us see how good
you really are.
Liza...
Do not interfere!
Stay here.
[WHACKS]
- [THUDDING]
- [GRUNTING]
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUDS]
- [THUDDING]
- [GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THUDS]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
You have proven
that you are skilled.
But you know,
I realized something...
I am not here to compete
or prove myself.
I am here to kill you!
I have an idea.
Do the honors, Jin Ho.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I will give you
the revenge you want.
Did she not betray you?
You understand that, right?
So do it!
This is your last chance
to prove your loyalty.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do it!
Do it now!
What are you waiting for?
Jin Ho, do not.
Please.
You...
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
You betrayed me, Joey.
So, that is your real name.
Have a safe trip to hell, Joey.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
The gunfire inside has stopped.
The police and DDE agents
may have finished it.
Hopefully, everyone
is being arrested now.
But, Joey...
we need to find her now.
Jin Ho, do it now!
I just wanted to give
that to you
so that wherever you are,
no matter where you go,
you will never forget
that you have friends.
You have us.
[CHUCKLES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
If you won't do it...
then I will.
- [GUN FIRING]
- [LIZA GROANING]
Let's go! Let's go!
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANING]
Traitors!
[GUN FIRING]
We have to leave now.
What?
When I count to three...
This is my car.
- You run, okay?
- Jin Ho, it is dangerous!
One, two, three!
Run!
[GUN FIRING]
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Andrew and Peter!
[GUN FIRING]
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What about Andrew and Peter?
Do not worry about them!
We need to go!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUN FIRING]
[GROANS]
[POLICE SIREN WAILING
IN DISTANCE]
Come on, let's go!
Let's go! Come on!
[GUN FIRING]
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Zoey, just hold on.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I thought I was going to die,
Sir.
There are still so many things
I want to do.
I want to be with
the person I love.
Zoey, you will do all of that
because you are going to live.
The DDE still needs you.
And besides,
we still have to take down
the syndicate, right?
Sir, we need to move her now.
All right.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
So, it was definitely an ambush.
They waited for all of us
to gather inside
before opening fire.
It was as if they knew a warrant
was about to be served.
They planned this in advance.
Sir, we have bad news.
Liza and Jin Ho escaped.
Have you alerted
the nearby stations?
Put out an alert...
with their vehicle descriptions.
We have already done that, Sir.
Good.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Andrew, I am asking you.
Do not report this
to your podcast yet.
Major, I am not here
to cover anything up.
I came here for Joey.
Joey?
Why?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho took him, Major.
What?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FROG CROAKING]
Ah, Jin Ho...
where are we now?
Why does it feel like
we are so far away?
There is not even any signal.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
About a hundred kilometers
from the warehouse.
Yes, it is far,
which means we are safe.
Are you sure this is safe?
It feels like we are
in a haunted forest.
Then you choose.
Death or Liza.
She is not finished with us yet,
Joey.
She will look for us.
So, we have to stay away
for a while.
For a while?
How long, Jin Ho?
Because...
of course, I need
to check on my father.
They need to know
that I am safe.
I will just try
to find a signal.
Go ahead.
If you can make it through
the darkness, go ahead.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
- [FROG CROAKING]
- [GECKO VOCALIZING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LOW BATTERY PROMPT CHIMES]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [FROG CROAKING]
- [GECKO VOCALIZING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I thought you were leaving?
My phone battery died.
Just go with me, okay?
I will open the gate.
Just stay here.
There might be monsters here,
you know.
Monsters are usually eat
the noisy ones.
[LIGHT PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUN COCKS]
Ah, Jin Ho...
Where exactly are we?
This is my last safe house.
Only people I trust
know about this.
So, we will just hide here?
Why do we not just report this
to my father?
Do you think Liza will give up
just because you told
the police?
She's really mad at you,
and me for helping you.
When she finds us,
she will kill us.
So, unless you want us both
buried tonight,
this is the safest place
we have.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, by the way, Jin Ho...
Why did you shoot Liza
instead of me?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Damn that Jin Ho!
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I could not chase after him
because the police
had already arrived!
[GROANING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- You said...
- [GROANING]
your plan was solid.
- You said...
- [GROANING]
you will handle it!
- You said...
- [GROANING]
You said that Jin Ho
would not betray us!
Look what happened!
You brought us a liability!
[GROANING]
Clean this mess up,
or next time, you will get more
than that from me.
Stand up.
[GROANS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why did you shoot Liza
instead of me?
[SIGHS]
I do not know, okay?
I do not even know
if I made the right choice.
You might turn me over
to the police in the end.
Jin Ho, if I wanted to do that,
I would have done it earlier.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I know you and Liza
have a history.
You even used us to find her,
right?
You just wanted to find her,
not to arrest her.
That is why I want to ask...
What happened?
Why did you break away from her?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You want to talk
to your parents?
I have a way.
Why did he take Joey?
What does he need from her?
Miguel, he might do something
to Joey.
Clarissa, they are tracing
the route of Jin Ho's vehicle.
Auntie Clarissa,
please do not be afraid.
Jin Ho is not a bad person.
I am sure he will not hurt Joey.
We cannot be sure about that,
Peter.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho is a member
of the syndicate,
and that syndicate
has been looking for Joey
for a long time.
But Jin Ho went against them,
right?
We saw that earlier ourselves.
Maybe he is just saving Joey.
Saving her?
If he is saving her,
why can we still
not contact her?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Here, you can call your father.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Tell him that you are okay.
Okay.
But...
you cannot tell where you are,
and keep it short.
They might trace the call.
If they do, it could lead Liza
straight to us.
Are we clear?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Clear.
- Good.
I saved you, Joey.
Prove to me that I made
the right choice.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE KEYS BEEPING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Hello, Dad?
Joey?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Joey!
Dad, are you okay?
I am at home.
I am here with your mother.
- Where are you?
- Joey, my child!
Joey, my child, where are you?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Ah, I am okay.
I am safe.
Please do not worry.
Joey, why did you go
with Jin Ho?
Please tell us
where you are right now.
Yes...
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Joey!
Joey!
The call was cut.
That is enough.
Okay.
Thank you.
Did I not tell you
that we have nothing to fear?
Joey is with Jin Ho.
He did not hurt her.
She is safe.
The things Joey was saying
are the exact same lines
used by kidnapping victims.
We cannot afford
to be complacent.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You were the one asking, right?
And she answered.
You heard her,
she was not crying.
Her voice was steady.
She did not sound afraid.
What are you talking about?
Which proves my point.
It is obvious
that someone was watching Joey.
Peter, what you are saying
is hard to believe,
and I do not trust
that Korean man.
Clarissa, I will not stop
until I find Joey.
That is a promise.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
I do not know
what condition she was in
when we got caught in the chaos.
Then the Korean syndicate
took him.
Do not move.
They got a lead.
They spotted Jin Ho's vehicle
on a toll camera.
Uncle, which toll gate?
At Sta. Monica.
Find Jin Ho as fast as you can.
The police are already moving
to find them.
We need to get to them first
because Jin Ho
will definitely give us up.
Remember, he saw me.
I am sorry, brother-in-law.
Instead of saving them, it looks
like you made things worse.
Jin Ho!
Jin Ho...